Jagdish Mehra Collection
University of Houston Libraries
- The Book Project
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - Paper by Albert Einstein (II) (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - Paper by Albert Einstein (III) (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - Physics and Reality (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - Physics and Reality (continued) (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - The Foundation of the Light Quantum (I) (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - The Foundation of the Light Quantum (II) (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - The Foundation of the Light Quantum (III) (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - The 1909 Situation of the Radiation Problem (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Manuscript Drafts of Chapters - Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - Introduction (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - Application of Probability (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - Consequence from the Light Quantum (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - Early History of the Theory (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - Einstein's Contribution (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - Einstein's Later Quantum Paper (I) (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - Einstein's Later Quantum Paper (II) (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - Physics and Reality (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - The Foundation of Light (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - The Foundation of Light Quantum (II) (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - The Foundation of Light Quantum (III) (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - The 1909 Situation of the Radiation Problem (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - Typescript Drafts of Chapters - Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - Jagdish Mehra Correspondence - Haar (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Jagdish Mehra Correspondence - Kilmister (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Jagdish Mehra Correspondence - Klein (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Jagdish Mehra Correspondence - Nathan (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Jagdish Mehra Correspondence - Pelseneer (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Jagdish Mehra Correspondence - Prigogine (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Jagdish Mehra Correspondence - Street (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Research Material (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Research Material (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Research Material (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Research Material (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Research Material (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Manuscript (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Manuscript (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript ( with correction) (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript ( with correction) (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Typescript ( Bound) (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Page Proof (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 21)
    Frieman, Lorraine
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 25)
    Furman, James M.
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 26)
    Glanz, Delbert E.
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 27)
    Olszewski, E.
  - Anatomy of Reality: Merging of Intuition and Reason - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 28)
    Sack, Jonas
  - Conceptual Development of Statistical Mechanics - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Conceptual Development of Statistical Mechanics - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Conceptual Development of Statistical Mechanics - Typescript (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Conceptual Development of Statistical Mechanics - Typescript ( with correction) (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Conceptual Development of Statistical Mechanics - Typescript (with corrections) (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Conceptual Development of Statistical Mechanics - Typescript (with corrections) (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Conceptual Development of Statistical Mechanics - Typescript (with corrections) (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Hilbert's Foundation of Physics, Pages 1-150 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Hilbert's Foundation of Physics, Pages 151-R83 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Project Notes and Outlines (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Project Notes and Outlines (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Research Material - Collected Typescript (about Van der Waals) (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Manuscript - Part I (translation and with letter) (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Manuscript - Part I (translation and with letter) (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Manuscript - Part II (translation and with letter) (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Manuscript - Part II (translation and with letter) (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Manuscript - Part II (translation and with letter) (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Manuscript - Part II (translation and with letter) (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Manuscript - Part III (translation and with letter) (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Manuscript - Part III (translation and with letter) (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - J.D. Van der Waals Book Project - Manuscript (photocopied) (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Planck's Half - Quanta: History of the Concept of the Zero - Point Energy - Manuscript (photocopied) (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Planck's Half - Quanta: History of the Concept of the Zero - Point Energy - Manuscript (photocopied) (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Planck's Half - Quanta: History of the Concept of the Zero - Point Energy - Typescript (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Planck's Half - Quanta: History of the Concept of the Zero - Point Energy - Typescript (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Planck's Half - Quanta: History of the Concept of the Zero - Point Energy - Typescript (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Planck's Half - Quanta: History of the Concept of the Zero - Point Energy - Typescript (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "From Being to Becoming: Time and Complexity in the Physical Science - Research Material (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "From Being to Becoming: Time and Complexity in the Physical Science - Research Material (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "From Being to Becoming: Time and Complexity in the Physical Science - Research Material (Box 82, Folder 42)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "From Being to Becoming: Time and Complexity in the Physical Science - Manuscript (Box 82, Folder 43)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "From Being to Becoming: Time and Complexity in the Physical Science - Typescript (Box 82, Folder 44)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "From Being to Becoming: Time and Complexity in the Physical Sciences" Typescript (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "From Being to Becoming: Time and Complexity in the Physical Sciences" Typescript (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "From Being to Becoming: Time and Complexity in the Physical Sciences" Typescript (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "Order Out of Chaos: Man's New Dialogue with Nature" Manuscript (with letter) (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "Order Out of Chaos: Man's New Dialogue with Nature" Manuscript (photocopied) (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Prigogine, Illya - "Order Out of Chaos: Man's New Dialogue with Nature" Typescript (photocopied) (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - The Interpretation of Quantum Mechanics - Page Proof (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - The Interpretation of Quantum Mechanics - Page Proof (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - The Interpretation of Quantum Mechanics - Page Proof (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - The Interpretation of Quantum Mechanics - Page Proof (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - The Physicist's Conception of Nature - Publication/ Promotional Materials (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - The Physicist's Conception of Nature - Publication/ Promotional Materials (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - The Physicist's Conception of Nature - Publication/ Promotional Materials (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - The Quantum Principle: Its Interpretation and Epistemology - Project Outlines (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - The Quantum Principle: Its Interpretation and Epistemology - Project Outlines (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - The Quantum Principle: Its Interpretation and Epistemology - Typescript (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - The Quantum Principle: Its Interpretation and Epistemology - Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Project Outlines (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Typescript (photocopied) (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Typescript (photocopied) (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Typescript (photocopied) (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Typescript (photocopied) (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Typescript (photocopied) (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Typescript (photocopied) (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 25)
    Beiglbock, W.
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 27)
    De Stefano, Francesco
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 28)
    Kibble, T.W.B.
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 29)
    Strathdee, John
  - The Scientific Biography of P.A.M. Dirac - Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 30)
    Rosewarne, Kathleen
  - Click here to proceed to Part III of the Finding Aid.
- Photograph
  - Feynman Negatives (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Richard Feynman Photograph Photocopies from Caltech Archives (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Mehra Photographs - Richard Feynman (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Diagrams that Feynman doodled for Mehra, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - In Front of Feynman Diagrams (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - In his Office (by Mehra), 1962 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - In his Office (by Mehra), 1962 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - French Vogue Photo, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - With son Carl (Caltech Archives) (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - With son Carl and daughter Micelle (Caltech Archives) (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - With Gweneth Feynman and son Carl, Press Conference at the Atheneum, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - With Gweneth at Birth of son Carl (Caltech Archives), 1961 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Feynman with his son Carl (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Sign Hung at Caltech after Feynman's Death (by Robert Paz), 1988 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Caltech, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Casual Portrait (Caltech Archives), 1974 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Caltech (by Floyd Clark), 1974 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Caltech Commencement Address (Caltech Archives), 1974 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Formal Portrait (Caltech Archives) (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Richard Feynman (by Robert Paz, Caltech Archives) (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Caltech, 1950's (by Dr. Mehra) (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Receiving Neils Bohr International Gold Medal from Queen Margrette of Denmark, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Sign Hung on Throop Hall, Caltech, after Feynman Receives Nobel Prize, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Receiving Nobel Prize from King Gustan Adolf, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - After Receiving Nobel Price, Stockholm, Sweden, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Challenger Disaster Hearing, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Challenger Disaster Hearing, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Beat of a Different Drum Plates (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Beat of a Different Drum Plates (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Beat of a Different Drum Sketches (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Symposium, Lake Travis, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - Caltech Seminar Dar, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Past Decade in Particle Theory Symposium, Austin, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - Past Decade in Particle Theory Symposium, Austin, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - Past Decade in Particle Theory Symposium, Austin, TX, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Past Decade in Particle Theory Symposium, Austin, TX, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 36)
  - Past Decade in Particle Theory Symposium, Austin, TX, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 37)
  - Shelter Island Conference (by Robert Marshak), 1947 (Box 84, Folder 38)
  - Playing Percussion in South Pacific, Caltech (Caltech, Archives), 1981 (Box 84, Folder 39)
  - Playing bongos at Caltech Play Rehearsal, 1960's (Caltech Archives) (Box 84, Folder 40)
  - Feynman with Bongos (Caltech Archives), 1956 (Box 84, Folder 41)
  - Playing Bongos, 1950's (Caltech Archives) (Box 84, Folder 42)
  - With Jagdish Mehra at Caltech, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 43)
  - With Jagdish Mehra at Caltech, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 44)
  - With Murray Gell-Mann, 1959 (Box 84, Folder 45)
  - With Murray Gell-Mann, 1959 (Box 84, Folder 46)
  - With Murray Gell-Mann, 1959 (Box 84, Folder 47)
  - With Murray Gell-Mann at Caltech, 1980's (Caltech Archives) (Box 84, Folder 48)
  - With Nobel Laureate Willy Fowler (on Feynman's left) (Box 84, Folder 49)
  - With Former Teaches Abram Bader and Joe Johnson at Far Rochasvay High School, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 50)
  - With P.A.M. Dirac at Relativity Conference, Warsaw, 1962 (Box 84, Folder 51)
  - With Arline Feynman (from original belonging to Elmer Heller), 1942 (Box 84, Folder 52)
  - Sir Isaac (Richard) Newton (Feynman) (Caltech Archives) (Box 84, Folder 53)
  - Kids Reading Book (photo from Feynman's office sent to Dr. Mehra) (Box 84, Folder 54)
  - Feynman Paintings (originals owned by Phil Platzman at Bell Labs) (Box 84, Folder 55)
  - Giovanella Exhibition Catalogs (commissioned by Mehra to paint portrait of Feynman from photograph) (Box 84, Folder 56)
  - Art and Technique of Giovanella (commissioned by Mehra to paint portrait of Feynman from photograph), 1974 (Box 84, Folder 57)
  - Wolf Beigelboeck with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Wolf Beigelboeck with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Count Bernadotte and wife with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Count Bernadotte with unidentified (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Hans Bethe with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Hans Bethe with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Hans Bethe (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Hans Bethe (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Neils Bohr (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Heinrich Boll (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Harish-Chandra with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Harish - Chandra (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Subrahmanyan Chandrasekhar (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Subrahmanyan Chandrasekhar (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Subrahmanyan Chandrasekhar (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Subrahmanyan Chandrasekhar with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Subrahmanyan Chandrasekhar with Marlis Mehra and Mrs. Chandrasekhar (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Leon N. Cooper with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Leon Cooper with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Leon Cooper (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - George Cvjinovich with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - P.A.M. Dirac with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - P.A.M. Dirac with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - P.A.M. Dirac with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - P.A.M. Dirac (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Max Dressner (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Friedrich Durrenmatt (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Friedrich Durrenmatt with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Freeman Dyson with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Freeman Dyson (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Charles Enz with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Charles Enz with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - John Kenneth Galbraith (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Otto Hahn (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Werner Heisenberg and Mrs. Heisenberg (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - Werner Heisenberg and Mrs. Heisenberg (Box 85, Folder 36)
  - Werner Heisenberg with P.A.M. Dirac (Box 85, Folder 37)
  - Werner Heisenberg with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 38)
  - Werner Heisenberg and Joachim (Box 85, Folder 39)
  - Werner Heisenberg with Wirtz (Box 85, Folder 40)
  - Werner Heisenberg with unidentified (Box 85, Folder 41)
  - Werner Heisenberg with unidentified (Box 85, Folder 42)
  - Werner Heisenberg (Box 85, Folder 43)
  - Werner Heisenberg (Box 85, Folder 44)
  - Aldous Huxley (Box 85, Folder 45)
  - Aldous Huxley with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 46)
  - Aldous Huxley with friends of Mehra (Box 85, Folder 47)
  - Joseph Jauch (Box 85, Folder 48)
  - Joseph Jauch with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 49)
  - Res Jost with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 50)
  - Res Jost (Box 85, Folder 51)
  - Hedge Kragn with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 52)
  - Sir K.S. Krishnan (Box 85, Folder 53)
  - Sir K.S. Krishnan with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 54)
  - R. Kubo (Box 85, Folder 55)
  - R. Kubo with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 56)
  - Willis Lamb, Jr. with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 57)
  - Willis Lamb, Jr. (Box 85, Folder 58)
  - K.V. Laurikainen with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 59)
  - Archibald MacLeish with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 60)
  - Archibald MacLeish (Box 85, Folder 61)
  - Peter McClintock and Wife (Box 85, Folder 62)
  - Jagdish Mehra and Others (Box 85, Folder 63)
  - Jagdish Mehra with unidentified (Box 85, Folder 64)
  - Jagdish Mehra (Box 85, Folder 65)
  - Jagdish Mehra (Box 85, Folder 66)
  - Jagdish Mehra (Box 85, Folder 67)
  - Jagdish Mehra (Box 85, Folder 68)
  - Jagdish Mehra (Box 85, Folder 69)
  - Jagdish Mehra (Box 85, Folder 70)
  - Jagdish Mehra (Box 85, Folder 71)
  - Phillip Morrison (Box 85, Folder 72)
  - Sir Neville Francis Mott (Box 85, Folder 73)
  - Yuval Ne'eman (Box 85, Folder 74)
  - Yuval Ne'eman with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 75)
  - Sir Rudolph Peierls with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 76)
  - Ilya Prigogine (Box 85, Folder 77)
  - Ilya Prigogine with Mehra (Box 85, Folder 78)
  - Negatives (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - S. Radhakrishnan (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Prince Raimondo with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Sir C.V. Raman with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Sir C.V. Raman with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Sir C.V. Raman with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Sir C.V. Raman with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Leon Rosenfeld (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Leon Rosenfeld with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Michel Romerio (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Michel Romerio with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Abdus Salam with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Abdus Salam with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Abdus Salam with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Clarisa Schwinger (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Julian Schwinger (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Julian Schwinger (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Julian Schwinger with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Julian Schwinger with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Julian Schwinger with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Julian Schwinger with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Julian Schwinger and unidentified with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - E.C.G. Sudarshan with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Kenji Sugimoto with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Kenji Sugimoto with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Sugimoto's son with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Sin-Hiro Tomonaga with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - John Hasbouck van Vleck (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Carl Friedrich von Weizsacher (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Carl Friedrich von Weizsacher with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Carl Friedrich von Weizsacher with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Carl Friedrich von Weizsacher with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Jerome Wiesner (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Eugene Wigner (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Eugene Wigner (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - Eugene Wigner with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Eugene Wigner with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Eugene Wigner and Mrs.Wigner (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - C.N. Yang with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - C.N. Yang with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 40)
  - Hideki Yukawa with Mehra (Box 86, Folder 41)
  - Neils Bohr, Werner Heisenberg, and P.A.M. Dirac (Box 86, Folder 42)
  - H.B.G. Casimir, Abdus Salam, Mehra, Mrs. Wigner, Herbert Jehle, and Paolo Budinich (Box 86, Folder 43)
  - H.B.G. Casimir, Mrs. Dirac, Abdus Salam, and Mehra (Box 86, Folder 44)
  - Mrs. Dirac, Abdus Salam, Mehra, and Mrs. Wigner (Box 86, Folder 45)
  - Charles Enz, David Finklestein, and unidentified (Box 86, Folder 46)
  - Rudolf Hagedorn, Sebastian von Horner, and Werner Heisenberg (Box 86, Folder 47)
  - President Theodor Heuss and Werner Heisenberg (Box 86, Folder 48)